cnas.org 2010-11-01

# CNAS Privacy Policy | Center for a New American Security

The Center for a New American Security values our visitors' private information and understands the need for security and trust surrounding such information.

The following policy outlines the ways in which we collect, store and use personally identifiable information in providing our products and services. Except for very limited exceptions further described in the remainder of this Privacy Policy, we do not share any personally identifiable information with third parties.

**Information Collection & Use **

For each visitor to our Website, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible). We collect only the domain name, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Website, and is only disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website.

_Event Registration_

In order to attend a CNAS event, you may need to first complete an online registration form or send us your contact details. We may use this information to contact you about the event for which you have registered, or a similar future event which we determine may be of interest to you.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.

_Email a Friend/Forward to a Colleague_

If you use referral services to tell a friend/colleague about our site or electronic newsletters, we will send your friend/colleague a one-time e-mail inviting him or her to visit the location you have specified. CNAS does not retain this information in our database.

**E-Mail Communications from CNAS**

_Event Announcements_

If you wish to subscribe to our event announcements or receive other materials, we will use your e-mail address to send the requested materials. We always provide a way to unsubscribe or opt out. Please see the “Manage Your Preferences” or “Opt-out” at the bottom of the email you receive to be removed from our mailing list.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

_Personally identifiable information_

We do not share personally identifiable information with third parties, except insofar as that information is required to fulfill a service, such as product fulfillment, that you have requested.

_Log Files_

Web site visits generate certain information that is automatically stored in log files, including Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp and clickstream data.

We use this information, which in itself does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

_Cookies_

We do not set any cookies.

_Ad Servers_

We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. 

**Links to Other Sites**

This web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by CNAS. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites.

**Access to and Removal of Personally Identifiable Information**

You may correct, update or remove your personally identifiable information by e-mailing us at [info@cnas.org](mailto:info@cnas.org), or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

**Security**

The security of your sensitive personal information is important to us. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice.  If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Website to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses.  If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Website periodically.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, or if you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the below addresses or phone number.

Center for a New American Security (CNAS)  
1301 Pennsylvania Ave. NW Ste 403  
Washington, DC 20004   
202.457.9400

_Last Updated: March 26, 2009_
